Dana Nobile

Marketing Strategist

DanaGNobile@Gmail.com | (631) 672-7576 | Tampa, FL | www.DanaGNobile.com

Professional Summary:

Marketing professional carrying nearly ten years' experience with a specialty in account management. Campaign strategy efforts yield an average of 50% increase in social media engagement, 30% increase in website traffic, and 20% increase in new lead generation. Successful email automation strategist, who earned eCommerce company \$15,000 revenue in one month (three times the historical record).

Skills:

	•	c
•	Campaign	Strategy

- Content Marketing
- Inbound Marketing
- Buyer Personas
- PPC Strategy
- Competitive Analysis
- Email Automation

- Lead Generation
- Keyword Research
- Blogging
- Hubspot
- Moz/ SEM Rush
- MailChimp
- HTML/CSS

- Google Search Console
- Google Analytics
- Facebook Bus. Mngr.
- WordPress
- Canva

Certifications:

- Hubspot, Growth Driven Design
- HubSpot, Inbound Marketing
- HubSpot, Inbound Marketing Agency
- HubSpot, Contextual Marketing
- HubSpot, Marketing Software

- HubSpot, Email Marketing
- HubSpot, Social Media Marketing
- Google, Advanced Google Analytics
- SEM Rush, SEO Fundamentals
- SEMRush, Keyword Research

Professional Experience:

Postali | Remote Marketing Agency

Jan. 2020 - Current

Content Writer

- Responsible for researching, crafting and editing blogs for legal marketing agency
- Duties include performing keyword research to increase SEO and organic brand awareness
- Blog topics range from attorney resources to marketing tactics applicable to the legal industry

Pure Dental Brands | St. Petersburg, FL

December 2018 – January 2020

Senior Marketing Account Manager

- Increased social media engagement by over 50%, and website traffic by 40% via lead generation
- tactics, landing pages, paid ads and email automation
- Responsible for directing corporate marketing department of Dental Service Organization
- servicing 60+ practices across the US, in 9 states with annual marketing budget of 2.8 million
- Counseled CEO on all marketing initiatives and responsible for driving marketing strategy
- Recruited and managed relationships with outside agencies, freelancers and consultants
- Created and implemented annual marketing strategy to grow revenue via website management,

- email campaigns, social media, direct mail, local advertising, reputation management, Google Listings, Google Ad Words, PPC, SEO, SEM
- Lead website production projects from inception to launch by partnering with content creation,
- design, development, SEO and video production teams

Lead by Sales, LLC | Tarpon Springs, FL

November 2017 - December 2018

Content Marketing Manager

- Increased social media presence (engagement, followers, leads) by 75%
- Executed email automation campaign to existing customers which earned 15K in revenue
- Responsible for developing and implementing creative content strategy for two in-house
- brands
- Directed projects and managed creative team including videographer, graphic designer,
- blogger, web developer, web designer, and digital ad spend agency
- Crafted and implemented workflow of projects, and content calendars, measuring metrics of
- success for each campaign
- Coordinated, planned and oversaw photo and video shoots

Marketing 2 Go | Remote Marketing Agency

November 2014 - November 2017

Marketing Account Manager

- Average increase of 30% in lead generation for each account
- Developed and executed marketing plans, content calendars and branding strategies for both
- B2B and B2C industries across multiple outlets including social networks, email campaigns,
- blogs and landing pages
- Focus areas of accounts: Real estate, property management and legal
- Developed, implemented Facebook and Instagram ads via Ads Manager
- Responsible for negotiating contracts and creating media packages within client's budget
- Strong ability to multitask and manage multiple brands, while developing deep understanding
- of a variety of business structures

Home & Self Defense Specialists | Palm Coast, FL

December 2010 - November 2014

Co-Owner and Marketing Manager

- Average annual sales increase 20% YoY via marketing efforts, and increased social media
- engagement by 80% overall. Promoted CWP classes via social media and print ads-increased
- average class average from 5 to 25 students, netting increase of over 2K per class
- Launched opening of a new retail and eCommerce store, including negotiating vendor
- contracts, buying inventory, competitive analysis, store layout/design, conceptualizing website
- Developed and led the execution of marketing and eCommerce plan among various customer
- segments and channels
- Managed all social media channels, maintained and managed company website, and designed
- and implemented email marketing campaigns
- Sought, established and managed vendor relations with wholesalers and outside advertising
- agencies
- Prepared collateral and strategy for trade shows to capture new leads
- Managed P&L statement and budget for entire company

Marriott Properties | Long Island, NY

June 2006 – December 2010

Marketing Coordinator

- Responsible for assisting Director of Sales & Marketing in advertising initiatives
- Managed the property's website
- Assisted in choosing ideal advertising platforms and drafted necessary items for each, including
- radio ad scripts, print design and digital marketing materials
- Represented brand and created print brochures and collateral for bridal expos as well as coordinated and manage on-site trade shows; and assisted with marketing content calendar

Pre-Professional Experience:

Hearst Publications | New York, NY Jan. 2006 - June 2006 | Intern Tallahassee Bride Magazine | Tallahassee, FL Dec. 2003 – May 2004 | Intern FSView FSU College Newspaper | Tallahassee, FL Jan. 2004 – May 2006 | Staff Writer

Education:

Florida State University | Bachelor of Science Degree | Marketing | 2006 University of Central Florida | Certification | Web Development & Coding Bootcamp | 2020